

CONTACT

Addres

Flat no 204, shah nest, lane no 4c sanjay park ,411032 pune

Phone

+919322611013

EDUCATION

2016-2018

DEPLOMA IN ENTC

MGM polytechnic college

2018-2021

B'TECH IN ENTC

PES college of Engineering

PRO.SKILLS

MachineLearning React , HTML, CSS

Kubernetes AWS Podman Azure Docker OpenCV Jenkins **Postgress** ArgoCD MySql CircleCI MongoDB Ansible **Terraform** JavaScript

Embedded System

Python **ELK** TensorFlow Grafana Selenium Loki Shell Script Prometheus Kustomize Thanos Ethical Hacking Grype & Capsule8

Faizan Ahmed Quazi

Fullstack, Machine learning, DevSecOps & SRE engineer

PROFILE

I am a DevOps Engineer, expertise in Containers ,Orchestration and CICD ,with multi Cloud skills on AWS and Azure,I had worked on manny project's here is the list of those, Algotradeing, pypestreem, RollGo, Intuit I was responsible to manage the kubernetes cluster and all deployment, Also I was responsible for writeing and manageing pipelines and CI opreations

EXPERIENCE

Ethical Hacker: - 2 Years

Android Devlopment :- 1.2 years

DevOps:- 2.8 years

2017-2019

Ethical Hacker

I had started my career as an Ethical Hacker.

Learned Tech Stack: Nmap, DDoS, ICMP flood attack, TCPdump, reverse TCP payload, Create Malware, Trojan attack, Android Payload Attack, Airmon-ng, Aircrack-ng, Wordlist attack, Tor, Dark web, Onion Router, Tor circuit, SSH Attack, Linux/Windows Payload, Kernel Mod, TWRP, SQL Injection

Bug revealed: PUBG Mobile (UDP DDOS attack), BATU (SQL injection)

2019-2020 1 Years 2 Month Android Devloper I Freelance

In the year 2019, I shifted towards Android Development. I learned the following tech stack: Flutter, Java, Gradle, Frontend, and Android Studio. I also worked on the following projects: Mine2gether and RoboWallet.

2021-2022 1 Year 4 Month DevOps | Mclansys

Android Development and Ethical Hacking sparked a lot of interest in me, leading me to switch to the Cloud and DevOps domain. I was selected for a DevOps engineer role at McLansys during my campus placement in engineering.

The tech stack I learned for this role includes Docker, Kubernetes, Ansible, Grafana, Prometheus, AWS, and Jenkins.

Projects: Algotradeing, CapitalBetting, Pypestreem

2022-Current

DevOps | Intuit

I have received three performance appreciation awards from this organization. I was responsible for managing the QAL, DEV, and PERF environment clusters in Kubernetes. I have written/optimized more than 47 lenkins pipelines for this organization. The organization adopted my advice to manage clusters with ArgoCD and use Kustomize to manage manifests and environments. I also worked on and completed more than seven tasks that were escalated by others.

Tech Stacks: Kustomize, ELK, Kafka, capsule8, grype, Kubernetes, Containers, CircleCl, ArgoCD, shell script, Python, Terraform, Selenium, Loki, Thanos, Postgres, Mysql, MSAAS, IDPS, SSO, Linux, API's, podman.